<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Foo Fighters on Daniel Schaaff</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/foo-fighters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Foo Fighters on Daniel Schaaff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.4</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 03:40:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/foo-fighters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/sound-city-and-the-analog-vs-digital-debate-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2013 03:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/sound-city-and-the-analog-vs-digital-debate-like/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;sound-city-and-the-analog-vs-digital-debate&#34;&gt;Sound City and the Analog vs Digital Debate&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like many of you, I recently watched the Sound City Documentary Dave Grohl put out.  It’s a given that I found it entertaining, afterall its overflowing with good Rock n Roll!  I’ve also heard the film discussed on many various talk shows, interviews, and podcasts as well as reviews.  Most of the discussions focus on one of two story arcs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first arc is the story of the Neve board Dave bought from Sound City when they closed.  In this arc much of the Sound City sound is attributed to this unique Neve console.  Dave Grohl goes as far as to say that he wouldn’t be where he is today if it weren’t for that board.  The discussion during Grohl’s appearance on the Marc Maron podcast certainly centered around this story.  The second story people are quick to latch on to is the analog vs digital debate.  A large chunk of the documentary revolves around big bad Pro Tools coming along and ruining both Sound City and the quality of modern music.  Sound City was an analog studio.  Period.  Everyone who recorded there tracked to tape.  Most of the artists featured in the documentary were tracking live as well.  These great artists are then compared to those tracking everything separately in Pro Tools before editing the crap out of it to creat an &lt;em&gt;artificial&lt;/em&gt; performance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/dave-grohl-continues-to-be-awesome-him-and-taylor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2013 18:08:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/dave-grohl-continues-to-be-awesome-him-and-taylor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x-xEr489gHY?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=http://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&amp;amp;w;=500&amp;amp;h;=281]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dave Grohl continues to be awesome. Him and Taylor Hawkins dressed up in vintage Rush atire and performed overture at Rush&amp;rsquo;s induction into the Rock n Roll Hall of Fame.  Hilarious.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a side note, I continue to be jealous of much rock n roll goes on in Dave Grohl&amp;rsquo;s life.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WTF with Marc Maron Podcast: Episode 353 - Dave Grohl</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/wtf-with-marc-maron-podcast-episode-353-dave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2013 00:39:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/wtf-with-marc-maron-podcast-episode-353-dave/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://hermitology.com/post/40860260712/wtf-with-marc-maron-podcast-episode-353-dave-grohl&#34;&gt;hermitologist&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;![](http://llnw.wbez.org/blog/insert-image/2011-May/2011-05-31/mzi.cedtdihh_medium.png)
&gt; 
&gt; 
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most of you who’ve been reading Hermitology or following Thrice over the years are probably well aware of how much I admire Dave Grohl and how much I’ve been inspired by what he’s done and continues to do. &lt;a href=&#34;http://wtfpod.libsyn.com/episode-353-dave-grohl&#34;&gt;Marc Maron had Grohl as a guest on the WTF Podcast this week&lt;/a&gt; and the conversation they had boosted that admiration and inspiration to a whole new level. It’s an absolute must-listen. I could have listened to them chat for hours. &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
