<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Parenting on Daniel Schaaff</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/parenting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Parenting on Daniel Schaaff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.4</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 22:35:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/parenting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/taking-the-first-step-into-our-fears-watching-my/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 22:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/taking-the-first-step-into-our-fears-watching-my/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;taking-the-first-step-into-our-fears&#34;&gt;Taking the first step into our fears&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watching my children continues to teach me valuable lessons. The big decisions in life are tough and we often put off making a decision as long as possible due to fear and anxiety. This leads to procrastination and can be crippling at times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started thinking about this while interacting with my oldest daughter at the waterpark a few weekends ago. In the kids pool area there were 3 waterslides.  She would happily slide down the smaller two but steadfastly refuse the &lt;em&gt;slightly&lt;/em&gt; larger slide.  My one and a half year old twins even rode the larger slide but that did little to sway the strong willed 3 year old. In her mind it was a gargantuan waterfall.  On the second day there I continued to plead with her to take plunge.  It would be so much fun I assured her but she couldn&amp;rsquo;t look past her fear.  As a last ditch effort I offered a treat in return for trying the slide.  Her expression immediately perked up at the sound of that magical word and she ran straight to the top of the slide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/ive-always-thought-jim-gaffigan-was-hilarious/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2013 02:17:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/ive-always-thought-jim-gaffigan-was-hilarious/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[youtube https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l0yzUuHBW3o?feature=oembed&amp;amp;enablejsapi=1&amp;amp;origin=http://safe.txmblr.com&amp;amp;wmode=opaque&amp;amp;w;=500&amp;amp;h;=281]&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve always thought Jim Gaffigan was hilarious.  His jokes about having a million children have always been funny, but I never would have imagined his family living on the top floor of a 5 story walk in a 2 bedroom apartment.  I though I was weird for having 3 kids in 2 bedroom apartment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Take a look, it&amp;rsquo;s a great interview.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(Source: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Must Let Go of Their Desires for Their Time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/parents-must-let-go-of-their-desires-for-their/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 19:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/parents-must-let-go-of-their-desires-for-their/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent months Tif has said a few times how weird it is that I&amp;rsquo;ve been the one stressing out.  While in reality we&amp;rsquo;ve both had our fair share of stress, I have been unusually stressed.  Really, I just feel helplessly overwhelmed at times.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been working to figure out why and restore my usual calm and peace.  Thinking through this today, one issue in particular came to mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parenting requires us to divorce ourselves from a lot of our own desires.  It is impossible to be selfish and a good parent.  It takes time to let go of things and I still find myself wishing I was more often able to play guitar, read a book, or just have a moment of peace.  This season of my life, however, is about moving my family to the forefront and placing those desires in second place.  One day they will be bigger, and going to school.  I can then play my guitar more to help me through the desperation of watching my children grow up faster then I&amp;rsquo;d like:)  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Day in the Life of...Our Insanity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/a-day-in-the-life-ofour-insanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 02:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/a-day-in-the-life-ofour-insanity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It turns out my wife is a fantastic writer.  She has written an excellent, entertaining, and thorough run down of what an average day for us looks like.  Raising a 2 year old while managing newborn twins is pretty hectic and challenging.  Its sometimes surprising that we&amp;rsquo;re surviving all of this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://mzschaaff.blogspot.com/2012/06/day-in-life-triple-insanity.html&#34;&gt;A day in the life…triple insanity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twins Ultrasound 10/28/11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/twins-ultrasound-102811/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 17:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/twins-ultrasound-102811/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We got to see the twins again today.  Twin A is slightly smaller and really active.  The little stinker was doing flips and waving during the ultrasound.  Twin B is slightly bigger and the more mellow twin.  Sounds like there&amp;rsquo;s a little Tif and a little me in there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://67.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ltsej38Ts01qbk10k.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ltsejzgEM91qbk10k.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Different Tragedy in Steve Jobs&#39; Death</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/a-different-tragedy-in-steve-jobs-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/a-different-tragedy-in-steve-jobs-death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I love Apple and the products they create.  I always had an interest in gadgets
but was too busy playing guitar and trying to keep an old Dell laptop working to
take it much further than that.  It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until I moved to Chicago and bought
my first Macbook Pro that I fell in love technology. There is something in the
design of Apple products that makes them a pleasure to use, and that is thanks
to the vision and genius of Steve Jobs.  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>today my life changed forever</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/today-my-life-changed-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 02:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/today-my-life-changed-forever/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We obviously knew Tif was pregnant. We were trying to have our second baby and
today was our first ultra sound. As the nurse started the ultrasound the first
thing she says is &amp;ldquo;uh oh, your having twins.&amp;rdquo;  Haha, funny joke.  I thought,
this nurse is funny. Then I see two sacs as she says &amp;ldquo;better you than me.&amp;rdquo;
WHAT!!! Turns out that there&amp;rsquo;s two babies in there. I started sweating. HOLY
CRAP! Twins!!Tif and I always said that we wanted two babies. I never
considered having more. I was good with two. Well, God had different plans.
This generation of Schaaff&amp;rsquo;s will number 5 just like the previous one. We&amp;rsquo;re
e excited, but if I&amp;rsquo;m to be transparent, I must admit I&amp;rsquo;m super scared. I was
already a little nervous about waking up all night again. Now I&amp;rsquo;m worried about
how the heck I&amp;rsquo;m going to take care of two newborns and a toddler! I already
know this will be the hardest thing we&amp;rsquo;ve ever done, but it will also be the
most rewarding. I definitely don&amp;rsquo;t know how we&amp;rsquo;re
gonna do it…but I know that we will. Please send up some prayer for us.
There will be a lot of logistical and personal challenges and we need all the
grace we can get.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
