<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Toddlers on Daniel Schaaff</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/toddlers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Toddlers on Daniel Schaaff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.4</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 19:25:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/toddlers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Parents Must Let Go of Their Desires for Their Time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/parents-must-let-go-of-their-desires-for-their/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 19:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/parents-must-let-go-of-their-desires-for-their/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent months Tif has said a few times how weird it is that I&amp;rsquo;ve been the one stressing out.  While in reality we&amp;rsquo;ve both had our fair share of stress, I have been unusually stressed.  Really, I just feel helplessly overwhelmed at times.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been working to figure out why and restore my usual calm and peace.  Thinking through this today, one issue in particular came to mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parenting requires us to divorce ourselves from a lot of our own desires.  It is impossible to be selfish and a good parent.  It takes time to let go of things and I still find myself wishing I was more often able to play guitar, read a book, or just have a moment of peace.  This season of my life, however, is about moving my family to the forefront and placing those desires in second place.  One day they will be bigger, and going to school.  I can then play my guitar more to help me through the desperation of watching my children grow up faster then I&amp;rsquo;d like:)  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Day in the Life of...Our Insanity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/a-day-in-the-life-ofour-insanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 02:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/a-day-in-the-life-ofour-insanity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It turns out my wife is a fantastic writer.  She has written an excellent, entertaining, and thorough run down of what an average day for us looks like.  Raising a 2 year old while managing newborn twins is pretty hectic and challenging.  Its sometimes surprising that we&amp;rsquo;re surviving all of this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://mzschaaff.blogspot.com/2012/06/day-in-life-triple-insanity.html&#34;&gt;A day in the life…triple insanity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
