<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Kids on Daniel Schaaff</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/kids/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kids on Daniel Schaaff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.4</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 22:35:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/kids/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/taking-the-first-step-into-our-fears-watching-my/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 22:35:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/taking-the-first-step-into-our-fears-watching-my/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;taking-the-first-step-into-our-fears&#34;&gt;Taking the first step into our fears&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watching my children continues to teach me valuable lessons. The big decisions in life are tough and we often put off making a decision as long as possible due to fear and anxiety. This leads to procrastination and can be crippling at times.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I started thinking about this while interacting with my oldest daughter at the waterpark a few weekends ago. In the kids pool area there were 3 waterslides.  She would happily slide down the smaller two but steadfastly refuse the &lt;em&gt;slightly&lt;/em&gt; larger slide.  My one and a half year old twins even rode the larger slide but that did little to sway the strong willed 3 year old. In her mind it was a gargantuan waterfall.  On the second day there I continued to plead with her to take plunge.  It would be so much fun I assured her but she couldn&amp;rsquo;t look past her fear.  As a last ditch effort I offered a treat in return for trying the slide.  Her expression immediately perked up at the sound of that magical word and she ran straight to the top of the slide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
