<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Cli on Daniel Schaaff</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/cli/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cli on Daniel Schaaff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.4</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/cli/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to Renew Consul Root CA Certificate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2021/renew-consul-root-ca-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2021/renew-consul-root-ca-certificate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Consul root CA is generated using the &lt;code&gt;consul tls ca create &lt;/code&gt; command. If created with the original options the root CA is only valid for a few years. After running production for a while you inevitably need to extend this certificate. To do so we need to generate and sign a new certificate using the existing private key. Consul does not provide any commands for doing so but it can be done using OpenSSL.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lets Encrypt Bug Requires Reissue of Certificates by Cert-Manager in Kubernetes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/cert-manager-bug-lets-encrypt-k8s-renewal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/cert-manager-bug-lets-encrypt-k8s-renewal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I received a fun email from Lets Encrypt today letting me know that they were revoking all of my certificates on March 4. The bug is described &lt;a href=&#34;https://community.letsencrypt.org/t/2020-02-29-caa-rechecking-bug/114591&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of my certificates are managed by &lt;a href=&#34;https://cert-manager.io/docs/&#34;&gt;cert-manager&lt;/a&gt; inside Kubernetes. This led to the fun challenge of figuring out how to force
a reissue of every certificate. There were 2 approaches that came up in the Kubernetes community slack.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Delete all secrets containing cert-manager issued certificates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>In Praise of the Bat Commandline Tool</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2019/in-praise-of-the-bat-command-line-tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2019/in-praise-of-the-bat-command-line-tool/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been working on helm charts a lot lately. For better or worse that has involved running &lt;code&gt;helm install —debug —dry-run…&lt;/code&gt; a lot to ensure things render correctly. It is much easier to parse that output when there is syntax highlighting. Enter [bat](&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/sharkdp/bat&#34;&gt;GitHub - sharkdp/bat: A cat(1) clone with wings.&lt;/a&gt;). I can &lt;code&gt;helm install —debug —dry-run… | bat -l yaml&lt;/code&gt; to get full syntax highlighting.  It’s a small thing but it makes a big difference.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
