<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Twins on Daniel Schaaff</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/twins/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Twins on Daniel Schaaff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.4</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 19:25:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/twins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Parents Must Let Go of Their Desires for Their Time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/parents-must-let-go-of-their-desires-for-their/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 19:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/parents-must-let-go-of-their-desires-for-their/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent months Tif has said a few times how weird it is that I&amp;rsquo;ve been the one stressing out.  While in reality we&amp;rsquo;ve both had our fair share of stress, I have been unusually stressed.  Really, I just feel helplessly overwhelmed at times.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been working to figure out why and restore my usual calm and peace.  Thinking through this today, one issue in particular came to mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parenting requires us to divorce ourselves from a lot of our own desires.  It is impossible to be selfish and a good parent.  It takes time to let go of things and I still find myself wishing I was more often able to play guitar, read a book, or just have a moment of peace.  This season of my life, however, is about moving my family to the forefront and placing those desires in second place.  One day they will be bigger, and going to school.  I can then play my guitar more to help me through the desperation of watching my children grow up faster then I&amp;rsquo;d like:)  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Day in the Life of...Our Insanity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/a-day-in-the-life-ofour-insanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2012 02:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/a-day-in-the-life-ofour-insanity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It turns out my wife is a fantastic writer.  She has written an excellent, entertaining, and thorough run down of what an average day for us looks like.  Raising a 2 year old while managing newborn twins is pretty hectic and challenging.  Its sometimes surprising that we&amp;rsquo;re surviving all of this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://mzschaaff.blogspot.com/2012/06/day-in-life-triple-insanity.html&#34;&gt;A day in the life…triple insanity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twins Ultrasound 10/28/11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/twins-ultrasound-102811/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 17:44:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/twins-ultrasound-102811/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We got to see the twins again today.  Twin A is slightly smaller and really active.  The little stinker was doing flips and waving during the ultrasound.  Twin B is slightly bigger and the more mellow twin.  Sounds like there&amp;rsquo;s a little Tif and a little me in there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://67.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ltsej38Ts01qbk10k.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_ltsejzgEM91qbk10k.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Twins&#39; Ultrasound 10.21.11</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/the-twins-ultrasound-102111/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2011 16:29:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/the-twins-ultrasound-102111/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We got to go see the twins again today.  It is amazing how much they are already moving around.  I could see their little arms and legs now!  The little tikes are healthy and everything is going well.  We were happy to hear that they each have their own placenta and sac, which is the most optimal condition for twins!  In the upper left hand corner of each picture is an A or a B.  A is one twin and B is the other.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>today my life changed forever</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/today-my-life-changed-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2011 02:52:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/today-my-life-changed-forever/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We obviously knew Tif was pregnant. We were trying to have our second baby and
today was our first ultra sound. As the nurse started the ultrasound the first
thing she says is &amp;ldquo;uh oh, your having twins.&amp;rdquo;  Haha, funny joke.  I thought,
this nurse is funny. Then I see two sacs as she says &amp;ldquo;better you than me.&amp;rdquo;
WHAT!!! Turns out that there&amp;rsquo;s two babies in there. I started sweating. HOLY
CRAP! Twins!!Tif and I always said that we wanted two babies. I never
considered having more. I was good with two. Well, God had different plans.
This generation of Schaaff&amp;rsquo;s will number 5 just like the previous one. We&amp;rsquo;re
e excited, but if I&amp;rsquo;m to be transparent, I must admit I&amp;rsquo;m super scared. I was
already a little nervous about waking up all night again. Now I&amp;rsquo;m worried about
how the heck I&amp;rsquo;m going to take care of two newborns and a toddler! I already
know this will be the hardest thing we&amp;rsquo;ve ever done, but it will also be the
most rewarding. I definitely don&amp;rsquo;t know how we&amp;rsquo;re
gonna do it…but I know that we will. Please send up some prayer for us.
There will be a lot of logistical and personal challenges and we need all the
grace we can get.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
