<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>ITunes on Daniel Schaaff</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/itunes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ITunes on Daniel Schaaff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.4</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 23:10:39 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/itunes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>iOS Music Players</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/ios-music-players/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Feb 2013 23:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/ios-music-players/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Pro tip.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On the desktop we’re mostly limited to using iTunes for music playback (aside from streaming services). If you don’t like iTunes, good luck finding a better alternative.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully the situation is different on an iOS device. Don’t like apple’s music app? Simply fire up the AppStore and download a 3rd party music player. I recommend checking out &lt;a href=&#34;http://ecouteapp.com/ecouteios/&#34;&gt;Ecoute&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;http://enderlabs.com/track-8&#34;&gt;Track 8&lt;/a&gt; , &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.zikeragroove.com/&#34;&gt;Groove 2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/streaming-vs-itunes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Dec 2012 05:00:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/streaming-vs-itunes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;streaming-music-services-vs-an-itunes-addiction&#34;&gt;Streaming Music Services VS an iTunes Addiction&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Music has been a huge part of my life for many years. I’m no longer a touring musician but I still play music as much as I can. Music is always playing in our house and I can’t imagine living life without it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Time has changed the way I listen to music a lot. I came of age in the era of the CD, but ever since I got my first iPod I’ve relied almost entirely on iTunes for my music consumption. At this point I’ve amassed a collection that would take 43 days to listen to.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Giving Away Music Makes Sense</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/giving-away-music-makes-sense/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jun 2012 22:19:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/giving-away-music-makes-sense/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A really good take on &lt;a href=&#34;http://derekwebb.tumblr.com/post/13503899950/giving-it-away-how-free-music-makes-more-than-sense&#34;&gt;the state of the music business&lt;/a&gt; as it relates to Spotify, piracy, iTunes, and money from Derek Webb.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll go even further to say that I actually prefer illegal downloading over Spotify because when you get music illegally it’s at least implicit in the transaction that what you’re doing is potentially harmful to the artist.  But with Spotify, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.mercurynews.com/breaking-news/ci_19361137&#34;&gt;your conscience is clear&lt;/a&gt; because you’re either enduring ads or paying to use the service and access the music.  But from the blue-collar artist’s perspective, they’re not receiving any meaningful payment (there’s &lt;a href=&#34;http://matthewebel.com/2011/07/20/spotify-let-the-money-pour-in/&#34;&gt;little discernible difference&lt;/a&gt; between $0.00029 and $0.00) and they are learning nothing about their fans, not to mention that music readily available on Spotify for little to no payment &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.hypebot.com/hypebot/2011/11/distributor-pulls-234-labels-from-spotify-napster-rdio-after-itunes-payments-drop-24.html&#34;&gt;completely poaches the record sales&lt;/a&gt; upon which middle-class musicians are depending for survival (which is why I will withhold any new releases from Spotify in the future).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Squaretrade Iphone 4 replacement and iCloud restore</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/squaretrade-iphone-4-replacement-and-icloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2011 19:29:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/squaretrade-iphone-4-replacement-and-icloud/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A couple weeks ago my iPhone developed a permanent vertical line down the right side of the screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://66.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_lvn6yvpwtQ1qbk10k.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a Squaretrade extended warranty on the phone so I filed a claim.
Squaretrade responded less than 12 hours later to request pictures.  It is
difficult to capture with a camera, but I did the best I could.  I emailed
Squaretrade these pictures at 9pm.  The next morning I already had a response in
my inbox saying my claim was approved and they would be overnighting a
(refurbished) replacement phone.  It was an incredibly easy process and
Squaretrade was a pleasure to deal with.  I also did not have to pay any form of
deductible since it wasn&amp;rsquo;t considered accidental damage (i.e. cracked screen,
phone in toilet).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
