<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Gmail on Daniel Schaaff</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/gmail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gmail on Daniel Schaaff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.4</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/gmail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Update on iCloud&#43; Custom Email Domain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/update-on-icloud-custom-email-domain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/update-on-icloud-custom-email-domain/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been using my custom domain with iCloud email for a couple weeks. Truth be
told I hardly notice any difference from when I used Gmail. That&amp;rsquo;s largely due
to using Apple Mail app as my primary interface. I haven&amp;rsquo;t had any reliability
issues and the only real difference I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed is the email size limit is
20MB as opposed to Gmail&amp;rsquo;s 25MB. The primary benefit I&amp;rsquo;ve seen is that
calendar invites end up on my iCloud calendar, which is where I prefer them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Migrating My Email From Google Workspace To iCloud&#43;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/migrating-from-google-workspace-to-icloud-plus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2024/migrating-from-google-workspace-to-icloud-plus/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m in the process of migrating my email from Google Workspace to iCloud+. I&amp;rsquo;ve
been using Google Workspace (aka gsuite, aka whatever name Google switches to
next week) for my email for a long time. For ages it was free and made perfect
sense as a service. Those free accounts have gone away, and the service&amp;rsquo;s focus
is clearly aimed at the enterprise and not individuals like me. The price per
user is also about to increase on me, so this felt like a good time to try
something else. I&amp;rsquo;m only really interested in hosting email for a few custom
domains and have no needs for any features beyond that. Our family already uses
iCloud for everything so I figured why not give it a try.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>google sure loves to disappoint</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/google-sure-loves-to-disappoint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2011 16:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/google-sure-loves-to-disappoint/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sure enough Gmail is live in the app store.  Unfortunately its not an entirely
native application.  Most of it is a native wrapper for a web view of the mobile
site.  We get push notifications(except that their broken right now), address
book integration, and the ability to attach photos, but the interface is a bit
laggy and still won&amp;rsquo;t format an html email to fit the screen.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be surprised.  Google usually releases products publicly before they&amp;rsquo;re ready and then slowly improves them.  Link to the app store below.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Native gmail app for iPhone!!!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/native-gmail-app-for-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2011 02:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/native-gmail-app-for-iphone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This would make me quite happy if it&amp;rsquo;s true.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://parislemon.com/post/12181169812/incoming-a-native-gmail-iphone-app-finally&#34;&gt;Native gmail app for iPhone!!!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make Gmail play nice with Apple Mail</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/make-gmail-play-nice-with-apple-mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2011 16:14:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/make-gmail-play-nice-with-apple-mail/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I determined a compromise.  I&amp;rsquo;m going to keep using iCloud for
contacts and calendars.  Google sync makes a mess of contacts, iCloud &amp;ldquo;just
works.&amp;rdquo;  I&amp;rsquo;ll keep using Gmail for my main email.  I&amp;rsquo;ll access it through Apple
Mail on the desktop and the iPhone&amp;rsquo;s built in mail app.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s how I set it up to avoid duplicate messages and other craziness.  Log
into Gmail&amp;rsquo;s settings and navigate to the labels tab.  Here you can control
which labels show up in IMAP.  What I did was hide all mail, starred, and
important from IMAP.  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gmail to iCloud to Gmail again...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/gmail-to-icloud-to-gmail-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 20:38:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/gmail-to-icloud-to-gmail-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve used Gmail or several years and have really enjoyed the experience.  It&amp;rsquo;s
not without its quirks however.  Anyone who has ever used Gmail with an IMAP
client can attest to how wonky things can get.  The way Gmail&amp;rsquo;s All Mail folder
functions causes lots of duplicate messages to show up.  If a message has a
label it will appear in both a folder for that label as well as in the All Mail
folder.  If you search for a message in the client multiple copies will pop up.
The Gmail experience on the iPhone is also annoying.  You can setup up Gmail
through IMAP just like a desktop client, with all of the duplicate messages, but
you can&amp;rsquo;t get push.  That means I have to set my phone to poll the network at a
certain interval.  This is bad for battery life at high settings and means that
messages don&amp;rsquo;t show up right away.  The other option is to set up Gmail though
Google sync as an exchange server.  You can get push with this option but
deleting a message will always archive it.  I don&amp;rsquo;t want to archive all the junk
newsletter messages I get.  To delete a message with this setup I have to select
it and then manually move it to Gmail&amp;rsquo;s trash folder.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
