<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Faith on Daniel Schaaff</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/faith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Faith on Daniel Schaaff</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.4</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 14:04:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/faith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Thought via Path</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/thought-via-path-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2013 14:04:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/thought-via-path-2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tony Stewart, former mega church pastor, provides a look at why he hasn’t attended church in over a year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://tonysteward.me/post/41420912985/i-havent-been-to-a-church-in-over-a-year&#34;&gt;http://tonysteward.me/post/41420912985/i-havent-been-to-a-church-in-over-a-year&lt;/a&gt; – Read on &lt;a href=&#34;https://path.com/p/2Cl3ra&#34;&gt;Path&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Parents Must Let Go of Their Desires for Their Time</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/parents-must-let-go-of-their-desires-for-their/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2012 19:25:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/parents-must-let-go-of-their-desires-for-their/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In recent months Tif has said a few times how weird it is that I&amp;rsquo;ve been the one stressing out.  While in reality we&amp;rsquo;ve both had our fair share of stress, I have been unusually stressed.  Really, I just feel helplessly overwhelmed at times.  I&amp;rsquo;ve been working to figure out why and restore my usual calm and peace.  Thinking through this today, one issue in particular came to mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parenting requires us to divorce ourselves from a lot of our own desires.  It is impossible to be selfish and a good parent.  It takes time to let go of things and I still find myself wishing I was more often able to play guitar, read a book, or just have a moment of peace.  This season of my life, however, is about moving my family to the forefront and placing those desires in second place.  One day they will be bigger, and going to school.  I can then play my guitar more to help me through the desperation of watching my children grow up faster then I&amp;rsquo;d like:)  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Would it even be worth it if you could go back and change the past?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/would-you-change-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 19:35:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2012/would-you-change-the-past/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tif and I have had a lot of conversations about whether we would change the past.  I always would say that are things I would absolutely like to change.  That&amp;rsquo;s where I naturally go with regret.  Tif didn&amp;rsquo;t think you could divorce what has happened in the past with who we are today and in a lot of ways I&amp;rsquo;ve come to agree with her.  Good or bad, where we are is a direct result of where we&amp;rsquo;ve been.  I had to learn to not dwell on things that had happened, but instead focus on where I was and where I was heading.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Different Tragedy in Steve Jobs&#39; Death</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/a-different-tragedy-in-steve-jobs-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2011 21:02:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2011/a-different-tragedy-in-steve-jobs-death/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I love Apple and the products they create.  I always had an interest in gadgets
but was too busy playing guitar and trying to keep an old Dell laptop working to
take it much further than that.  It wasn&amp;rsquo;t until I moved to Chicago and bought
my first Macbook Pro that I fell in love technology. There is something in the
design of Apple products that makes them a pleasure to use, and that is thanks
to the vision and genius of Steve Jobs.  &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
